export const questions: {
    question: string;
    options: string[];
    correctAnswer: string;
}[] = [
    {
      question: "What is the capital city of Morocco?",
      options: ["Marrakech", "Casablanca", "Rabat", "Fes"],
      correctAnswer: "Rabat"
    },
    {
      question: "Which mountain range is located in Morocco?",
      options: ["Andes", "Himalayas", "Atlas Mountains", "Rocky Mountains"],
      correctAnswer: "Atlas Mountains"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the official language of Morocco?",
      options: ["French", "Arabic", "Spanish", "Berber"],
      correctAnswer: "Arabic"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these cities is famous for its blue-painted buildings?",
      options: ["Agadir", "Chefchaouen", "Tangier", "Essaouira"],
      correctAnswer: "Chefchaouen"
    },
    {
      question: "What is Moroccoâ€™s national dish?",
      options: ["Sushi", "Paella", "Couscous", "Pizza"],
      correctAnswer: "Couscous"
    },
    {
      question: "Which ocean borders Morocco to the west?",
      options: ["Atlantic Ocean", "Pacific Ocean", "Indian Ocean", "Arctic Ocean"],
      correctAnswer: "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the currency used in Morocco?",
      options: ["Euro", "Dirham", "Dollar", "Pound"],
      correctAnswer: "Dirham"
    },
    {
      question: "Which famous film was shot in the city of Ouarzazate, often called the 'Gateway to the Sahara'?",
      options: ["Gladiator", "The Godfather", "Inception", "Avatar"],
      correctAnswer: "Gladiator"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the traditional Moroccan mint tea?",
      options: ["Chai", "Earl Grey", "Atay", "Rooibos"],
      correctAnswer: "Atay"
    },
    {
      question: "Which festival is celebrated annually in Marrakech, showcasing Moroccan culture and music?",
      options: ["Marrakech Popular Arts Festival", "Marrakech Film Festival", "Marrakech Food Festival", "Marrakech Jazz Festival"],
      correctAnswer: "Marrakech Popular Arts Festival"
    }
  ];
  